The poem.
Coming
out twixt
these
smackers.
It'll flow
over them
like they’re
some
Midwestern
frackers.
It'll be the
titular work:
ourhole.com
The friggin
last slow
dance of our
senior prom.
We sway back
and forth
a space
in between us.
Or screw it.
Smush flesh
together.
No room
for Jesus.
Revolve.
Rotate.
Shuffle
and slide.
In clouds
of balloons,
our secrets
can hide.
Then pause
and steady
yourselves
in a place
that feels
comfy.
Or screw it.
Sit on a wall.
We'll tempt
fate like
we're Humpty.
Cuz, uh
love,
LOVE is
out there.
And we'll
embrace
the fall.
Our poem.
The poem
will comfort
us all.
Now the poem,
the poem,
the poem is
so near.
But, ugh
this art is
too long
for our ear,
we may
fear.
BUT
dang,
we're in it.
We've stayed
for this long.
We've shifted
our weight.
We've
picked at
our thong.
We've looked
all around us
and mapped out
our route
next to that
painting,
white wine,
then we're out.
So we wait.
Sure,
we can see
this thing
through.
If
Sisyphus
is happy,
we can be, too.
Imagine
it's just us
and poem
on our
own device.
This box in
our hand.
ooooooh
Damn,
it feels nice.
We rub it
all over
in between
thighs.
If
judgment
could melt
from their
judgy
judge eyes.
They watch us,
we know it.
They creep
as we crawl.
Finding
ourselves in
this womb
of it all.
So we wait...
When poem
is done.
And we're
all alone.
Doors
can be locked.
Touchscreen
digits
can roam.
And pinch
becomes pull,
swipe
on the
swelling.
We zoom in
on futures
that they
are selling.
Hold on.
Stop.
Back to
this matter
of starting
a verse.
Tabula rasa
To start...
what a curse.
But
in the meantime,
let's consider
this question
and let
thoughts
become real.
Start
the
ingression.
Do we need
a rostrum
or a restroom?
A dais
or bidet?
I mean,
it seems
our hole
will abide;
out comes poo
either way.
And once
excrement’s
gone
and we're left
feeling empty.
And they've
studied our
poo like
some poo.
cognoscenti,
our hunger
buzz
tix
AYCE buffet
And we BOGO
together
half and half,
like coffee.
And marvel
before us:
Everything
we could want.
Amazon®-ed
by the bounty
of this
endless food
font.
Golden Corral®-ed
by the gods
to witness
their mercy.
They give us
it all
for a
minuscule
purse fee.
And we'll
take it.
We'll take it.
Munch
munch
munch munch
munch.
The way we eat
croutons
will be
Captain
Crunch.
We'll scream,
“Let us eat
lettuce, you.”
“Olive you
to pits.”
“I'll toss
your salad.
I'll bacon
you to bits.”
“Cuz
we feed
each other.
We make a Full House.”
But then
over comes
Kimmy,
warning
of Faust.
And we're
like,
“Kimmy,
you're
fiction.
Your life
is not real.”
Anyway,
we're not
selling
our souls.
We're
embracing
the zeal.
Kimmy’s a doodoo
with doodoo
for brains.
Free your
mind, Kimmy
Unhinge those
chains.
Then we’re
back.
Back to
the poem.
The truth of
the matter.
The place
we'll
call home.
It will be
more than
real.
Something
perfect
from us.
Something
with layers
of meaning
that critics
discuss.
A volcano
of new,
not dripping
pus.
A thing
so good
they would be
nonplussed.
Something
pushing
past genius
that never
was rushed.
Some new
type of beauty
that causes
a fuss.
A revelation,
a light
through
the dust,
a boom
on the surface
to shatter
the crust.
The tastiest
thing
they'll
ever degust
to make are
millions
are kids
get their
trust.
The city
erects
our face
as a bust.
Ready
the hips,
wind up,
and thrust.